<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Teun van Veggel | Nuez | Independent Drupal Developer on Hi, I am Teun [nuez]</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Teun van Veggel | Nuez | Independent Drupal Developer on Hi, I am Teun [nuez]</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Delft</title>
      <link>/projects/delft/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/delft/</guid>
      <description>Drupal voor Gemeenten (Drupal for local governments) is a Drupal installation profile for websites for local authorities. It implements proven concepts to make local goverment websites as intuitive and user-friendly as possible. The Drupal 7 version is currently used in over 30 websites for local goverments in the Netherlands. Delft is the first use case for the Drupal 8 version.
I was asked to build the port of Drupal voor Gemeenten to Drupal 8, while at the same time developing the specific use case of the city of Delft website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flean</title>
      <link>/projects/flean/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/flean/</guid>
      <description>What started out as one of most successful holiday rental websites in the Netherlands, www.fijnopvakantie.nl, grew out to be a full-service, hosted holiday rental solution, currently serving than 20 holiday rental websites.
The platform allows holiday park owners to increase revenue and improve conversion with a customizable, full-fledged solution taking care of bookings, processing availability (connecting to more than 10 different external booking services) and many other functionalities.
For this project I have worked on a &amp;lsquo;full-stack&amp;rsquo; range of features: I helped professionalising DevOps and deployment strategies, built new features such as SendGrid integration and implemented new designs and elements with Angular2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOI Business School</title>
      <link>/projects/eoi/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/eoi/</guid>
      <description>For this project I was lead developer and product owner, working together with FrontID In the first phase of this project we defined and built a new, sustainable, architecture in Drupal and migrated hundreds of thousands of contents coming from LifeRay.
The original, static HTML pages of the old website were migrated to dynamic and flexible pages: site editors can now create slideshows, tabs and accordions on the fly and drag and drop them freely into the design without any requiring programming knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midleton School</title>
      <link>/projects/midleton/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/midleton/</guid>
      <description>In the course of more than 5 years I&amp;rsquo;ve worked together with Midleton School to build custom solutions to improved workflows and save time and money.
###Download area I developed</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes</title>
      <link>/testimonies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/testimonies/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;The work of Teun and his team has been exceptional, always putting in that bit of effort to propose solutions to any problem. Always prepared to think of the benefits for the client. Their ample experience and professionality guaranteed the success of the project.&amp;rdquo;
 Enrique Torras - Project Manager - Escuela de Organización Industrial (EOI) &amp;nbsp;
 &amp;ldquo;We&amp;rsquo;ve been working for several years with Teun and we&amp;rsquo;re very happy with the work he&amp;rsquo;s done for us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/talks/</guid>
      <description> 
   About Where When     Configuration Schema in Drupal 8 DrupalDay Spain 2017, Cáceres, Spain November 2017   Test Driven Development in Drupal 8 DrupalCamp Spain 2017, Madrid, Spain May 2017   Test Driven Development in Drupal 8 Meetup Drupal Noord, Groningen, Netherlands February 2017   Entity API in Drupal 7 DrupalCamp Spain 2013, Cáceres, Spain May 2013    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to unit test methods that create entities in Drupal.</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-unit-test-methods-that-create-entities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-unit-test-methods-that-create-entities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Recently I tried to create a Unit test for a Drupal service that creates and returns entities. &lt;strong&gt;In my test I wanted to check if the field values that were used for creating those entities were matching my assertions.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Drupal , the static &lt;code&gt;::create&lt;/code&gt; method of any content entity returns the created entity. In my unit test, checking the returned entity for values would be a hassle, as I would have to mock and stub my way through all the services that it relies on to fetch those values. More useful would be to mock the entity and let the  &lt;code&gt;::create()&lt;/code&gt; method return the values that were just passed as arguments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;¿Does that make any sense?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let me try and explain:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a super simple availability calendar.</title>
      <link>/posts/calendar-for-freelancers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/calendar-for-freelancers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a freelancer I like my (potential) clients to be aware of my availability. I decided to build something that would allow me to fill in my availability in Google Calendar, which would then be displayed in a nice widget on the website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The widget doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to display anything but whether or not I am available or busy on a certain day. I figured that the good ol&amp;rsquo; jQuery Datepicker would do perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here&amp;rsquo;s what I did.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&#34;1-get-an-api-key&#34;&gt;1. Get an API Key.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you google for accessing the Google API, most forums will point you in the direction of the OAUTH2 protocol. Using OAuth would be necessary if we wanted to access restricted content. For accessing publicly accessible content, the Google API is a lot easier. All you need is an URL and an API key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Go to &lt;a href=&#34;https://console.developers.google.com&#34;&gt;https://console.developers.google.com&lt;/a&gt; and create a new project. Select &lt;code&gt;credentials&lt;/code&gt; and create an &lt;em&gt;API Key&lt;/em&gt;.  You can restrict the use of the key although you don&amp;rsquo;t have to. Copy the API key value somewhere: we&amp;rsquo;ll need it in our code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create computed fields in Drupal 8.</title>
      <link>/posts/computed-fields-drupal-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/computed-fields-drupal-8/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;I have updated this post as a result of &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.drupal.org/project/drupal/issues/2392845&#34;&gt;the issue (https://www.drupal.org/project/drupal/issues/2392845)&lt;/a&gt; that added the  &lt;code&gt;ComputedItemListTrait&lt;/code&gt; trait to core.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Drupal 8 we have on the one hand field types with some computed &lt;strong&gt;field properties&lt;/strong&gt;, and on the other hand fields that are fully computed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Computed field properties are quite common in Drupal 8. An example is the &lt;code&gt;TextItem&lt;/code&gt; field type. The properties &lt;code&gt;value&lt;/code&gt; and &lt;code&gt;format&lt;/code&gt; are stored in the database, but a third property called &lt;code&gt;processed&lt;/code&gt; is computed on the fly using the &lt;code&gt;value&lt;/code&gt; and the &lt;code&gt;format&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When it comes to fully computed field items, there are less examples in core. It seems that in Drupal 8.5 the only fully computed field is the &lt;code&gt;moderation_state&lt;/code&gt; field, provided by the Content Moderation module. The field is added to all entities that add a moderation workflow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since the &lt;code&gt;ComputedItemListTrait&lt;/code&gt; was added in &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.drupal.org/project/drupal/issues/2392845&#34;&gt;this issue&lt;/a&gt;, however, adding a computed field has become A lot more straightforward than it seems.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo vs Drupal: Why I used Hugo for my Drupal portfolio website.</title>
      <link>/posts/hugo-vs-drupal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugo-vs-drupal/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.drupal.org&#34;&gt;Drupal&lt;/a&gt; is a full-fledged CMS for secure and complex websites and applications and is adopted by many big companies and governments accross the globe. &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; is a static site generator built in GoLang that is blazing fast and quickly gaining popularity. For this website about my Drupal work I decided to go for Hugo. Here&amp;rsquo;s why.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hire me</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Use the form below or an email to teun@nuezweb.com to enquire about my rates and availability. Please include as much relevant information as possible about budget, scope, starting dates and deadlines.
   My agenda  Busy Available for hire  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DrupalCamp Spain</title>
      <link>/projects/drupalcamp/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/drupalcamp/</guid>
      <description>We developed the the DrupalCamp Spain website not only as a point of information for the DrupalCamp Spain 2017,but also as a blue print for future Drupal Camps and a case study for Best practices in Drupal 8. The code base is publicly accessible on Github
The website is branched off the Drupal Composer project, meaning that all dependencies can be installed using Composer (including contributed modules and core), keeping the GIT repository for the project itself clean and tidy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Loesche</title>
      <link>/projects/loesche/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/loesche/</guid>
      <description>For the German industrial engineering company Loesche I designed and developed a super flexible, multilingual website, using Paragraphs to guarantee maximum flexibility for the editors of the website.
The whole website was realised in just over a 100 hours including design and development.
 https://www.loesche.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>COIT &amp; AEIT</title>
      <link>/projects/coit/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/coit/</guid>
      <description>www.coit.es www.aeit.es  The websites for the COIT (The ofical Spanish Institute of Telecommunication Engineers) and the AEIT (it&amp;rsquo;s sister member asociation) were designed and built from scratch, included complex migrations and ended up brimming with advanced restricted access functionalities and workflow automizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crisnail</title>
      <link>/projects/crisnail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/crisnail/</guid>
      <description>http://www.crisnail.com  We were responsible for both the design and development of this multilingual website for professional nail products Crisnail, featuring a product showcase and a restricted area for professionals to download instruction and publishing materials.
It also features a dynamic Nail studio which generates images for different colors and styles automatically, using a custom programmed Drupal &amp;lsquo;Image style&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>