<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Drupal on Teun van Veggel/nuez.io - Freelance Drupal developer</title>
    <link>http://nuez.io/tags/drupal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Drupal on Teun van Veggel/nuez.io - Freelance Drupal developer</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://nuez.io/tags/drupal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace In Art</title>
      <link>http://nuez.io/projects/aceinart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nuez.io/projects/aceinart/</guid>
      <description> Custom Design and implementation using SASS Advanced workflow for published and moderated content www.aceinart.com  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crisnail</title>
      <link>http://nuez.io/projects/crisnail/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nuez.io/projects/crisnail/</guid>
      <description>http://www.crisnail.com  We were responsible for both the design and development of this multilingual website for professional nail products Crisnail, featuring a product showcase and a restricted area for professionals to download instruction and publishing materials.
It also features a dynamic Nail studio which generates images for different colors and styles automatically, using a custom programmed Drupal &amp;lsquo;Image style&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EOI Business School</title>
      <link>http://nuez.io/projects/eoi/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nuez.io/projects/eoi/</guid>
      <description>www.eoi.es  For this project I was lead developer and product owner, working together with FrontID In the first phase of this project we defined and built a new, sustainable, architecture in Drupal and migrated hundreds of thousands of contents coming from LifeRay.
The original, static HTML pages of the old website were migrated to dynamic and flexible pages: site editors can now create slideshows, tabs and accordions on the fly and drag and drop them freely into the design without any requiring programming knowledge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBP Uniuso</title>
      <link>http://nuez.io/projects/uniuso/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nuez.io/projects/uniuso/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>