<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Hi, I am Teun [nuez]</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Hi, I am Teun [nuez]</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How to unit test methods that create and return entities in Drupal.</title>
      <link>/posts/how-to-unit-test-methods-that-create-and-return-drupal-entities/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/how-to-unit-test-methods-that-create-and-return-drupal-entities/</guid>
      <description>Recently I tried to create a Unit test for a Drupal service that creates and returns entities. In my test I wanted to check if the field values that were used for creating those entities were matching my assertions.
In Drupal , the static ::create method of any content entity returns the created entity. In my unit test, checking the returned entity for values would be a hassle, as I would have to mock and stub my way through all the services that it relies on to fetch those values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to build a super simple availability calendar.</title>
      <link>/posts/calendar-for-freelancers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/calendar-for-freelancers/</guid>
      <description>As a freelancer I like my (potential) clients to be aware of my availability. I decided to build something that would allow me to fill in my availability in Google Calendar, which would then be displayed in a nice widget on the website.
The widget doesn&amp;rsquo;t need to display anything but whether or not I am available or busy on a certain day. I figured that the good ol&amp;rsquo; jQuery Datepicker would do perfectly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create computed fields in Drupal 8.</title>
      <link>/posts/computed-fields-drupal-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/computed-fields-drupal-8/</guid>
      <description>I have updated this post as a result of the issue (https://www.drupal.org/project/drupal/issues/2392845) that added the ComputedItemListTrait trait to core.
In Drupal 8 we have on the one hand field types with some computed field properties, and on the other hand fields that are fully computed.
Computed field properties are quite common in Drupal 8. An example is the TextItem field type. The properties value and format are stored in the database, but a third property called processed is computed on the fly using the value and the format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hugo vs Drupal: Why I used Hugo for my Drupal portfolio website.</title>
      <link>/posts/hugo-vs-drupal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/hugo-vs-drupal/</guid>
      <description>Drupal is a full-fledged CMS for secure and complex websites and applications and is adopted by many big companies and governments accross the globe. Hugo is a static site generator built in GoLang that is blazing fast and quickly gaining popularity. For this website about my Drupal work I decided to go for Hugo. Here&amp;rsquo;s why.

When I started building my new portfolio website, I decided to look further than Drupal to build it.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>